These are shells from two kinds of shellfish: snails and bivalves.
Clams, scallops and mussels are bivalves.
The conch and turban shells are from snails.
Whoa...
Inside the shell, their bodies are very soft, which is why they’re also called molluscs.
So that’s why they use a hard shell to protect themselves.
Oh! Now that I think of it...
Hm?
Escargon has a shell too!
...Right. Snails are a type of shellfish that went onto land.
So that guy’s nothing but a shellfish, huh.
Someone must be gossiping about me...
Forget about potential slander, come give this a taste.
Boy, grilled turban shell is the best!
Don’t be shy, come on.
I don’t want that sort of thing.
Why’s that?
I just don’t like it.
Not even with the smell of cooking soy sauce…
Here, try.
Hmph!
You’re a weird guy if you don’t like this stuff.
Soldiers, clean up those shells.
Hm? A shell?
Speaking of shells...
Don’t you gotta shell like that?!
...shell like that… shell like that...
Escargon Exposed
Wait! Escargon!
I just want to take a closer look at you!
That’s exactly what I don’t want!
Why are you being so stubborn about this?!
Why you little…!
You’ll never hit me with hammer skills like th- whoa!
Hehe, over here!
Stop being so shellfish!!
Looks like they’re fighting again.
Are those two on good terms or not?
They get along fine when they’re doing something bad, yet they fight over all sorts of trivial things.
Let’s go get a snack, Kirby.
Snack!
Can’t catch meee!
Too light on my feet.
Nyeeh!
Wait!
The years are catching up to you, Your Majesty.
Now if you’ll excuse me.
Dropped your guard!
That’s not fair!
Your blunder was turning your back on your enemy.
It’s starting to crack here.
A crack?! I can’t see.
Well well, so you’re really a shellfish after all?
That answers that question!
Shellahahahahaha...
This is no laughing matter!
Oh I’m breaking out in a cold sweat..
Help!
What?!
Escargon?!
What’s wrong?
Please help! You have to get me to a hospital.
Hos’pal?
Well well… Ah, this is… I see...
H-How is it?
It’s perfect. There’s a splendid crack forming.
Huh?! Then fix it!
It’s going to split no matter what.
Haaa?!
There’s no chance of recovery.
Hahaa?!
It’s going to split more.
It what?!
Ah… eeh… I…
OH MY GOD!!
Escargon.
Do you have to make such a big deal over it?
My shell isn’t like your clothes- it’s like my spine!
Hey, Yabui! Escargon’s bound to be here!
Yabui! Are you here?
Escargon?
Hm?
That’s odd, Yabui, your door won’t open.
Open the door while I still feel like a nice chat.
I’m hospitalized with a severe illness
for the next 80 years, so leave me alone!
Oh Escargon that’s terrible.
That’s why I’ve come to visit.
Don’t you worry
Es… car… gon!
This is the worst experience of my life.
Escargon!
Oh, no!
Dedede! If Escargon’s shell cracks any more, he won’t be able to conceal himself!
Conceal himself?
If the shell comes off completely, Escargon would be naked.
Escargon would be naked?!
I’ve never thought about what’s inside Escargon’s shell before.
But it's gotta be absolutely fascinating!
I wanna see what your body’s like!
Nobody seriously cares about that, right?
Actually...
Augh I can’t trust any of you!
I’ll treat it for you! Open the door!
Eek! Don’t open it!
What are you being so shy for?!
Me and you are friends!
Don't clam up!
Come out of your shell a bit!
Just leave... me... alone!
...a little help?!
I’ll have to use force!
It cracked...
Aw, it closed up. Get off there, Kirby.
Kirby, don’t move!
Don’t you see what you’ve done?
Now it’s cracked completely!
Demon! Ogre! Brute! Fatso! Sadist!
Don’t get mad, just let me check your injuries.
Don’t look at me...
You saying that only makes me want a better look.
Noooo don’t look!
Show me!                     No!
Get away!                         If you show me!!
Stop!                       When you show me!
We have the sort of relationship where we washed each other’s backs in the hot springs last autumn!
Oh wow!
Oh no!
Oh yay…
Po-yay?
That’s enough!
Dedede, you have to repay Escargon for his shell.
Re...pay? Replay? Relay?
It means make up for the damages! Find a way to restore his shell!
You hear that?!
You want to change your shell?
Alright, I got just the thing!
If it isn’t His Majesty. How can I help you today?
Escargon’s shell broke completely in half!
His shell was broken?
Then His Excellency has regressed to a mere slug?
I don’t know what he is, but I’m ordering a replacement shell!
Understood.
However, as this is a custom order, the cost and time needed will be higher.
It can be as late and expensive as you want as long as I get to have plenty of fun in the meantime.
Done.
Whew, it all turned out okay...
But look here, you all!
I’m afraid of moving with this packing tape on me!
We wrapped it with plenty so it should be
okay even if you move around a lot.
This is just a stop-gap measure!
Yabui! You’re a doctor, so isn’t it your job to do something to fix me?
I don’t know anything about molluscs, they disgust me.
Maybe if we use a really strong glue?
That’ll have to do.
But won’t you have to remove the shell to apply the adhesive?
No way?!
So basically like a change of clothes?
Let’s all split up and find a new shell he can change into.
This jar is from an ancient Pupupu civilization...
I don’t even care if it’s fake, I just need to borrow a bigger jar!
Bigger…?
Just borrowing this for a bit!
Stop! I need that for my business!
Oh?
And what are you using wool for?
That’s a secret.
A big secret!
Hey now, that isn’t something you can eat.
That’s just an empty shell.
Oh boy….
A vase, a pot, a tub and some wool.
These are supposed to be my shell for the time being?
Pick the one you like.
One I like…  Right, of course, how could I ever choose...
..from this kind of GARBAGE!? Ugh!
What about that way, Bun?
All clear!
Nothing out of the ordinary here, Fumu.
If his Majesty is such a stalker, I wonder how far he’d go?
If he wants to see him, he’ll do whatever it takes.
Escargon, the coast is clear.
I’m counting on you?
Whatever you do, don’t peek!
Yeah yeah.
Did Escargon take it off yet? Did he?
Shut up! If you peek I’ll never forgive you!
If I want to see, I really will do whatever it takes.
Really, what did I do to deserve this…
Well let’s start with the tub.
Oh, that’s good!!
Yeah, take it off!!
What the hell are you?!!
It was destroyed! My raging desire for knowledge has been trampled!
Are you okay, Escargon?
Eeeeek!
Sorry….
This is a bit much.
I’ll just have to try them all on!
A pot!
So weird...
A sheep’s wool! Baaah! So cute!
Even weirder!
Pupupu jar!
So old fashioned!
This is tragic!
How goes it, Fumu?
Does the glue work?
It’s tricky.  But it’s certainly interesting inside.
It is?
I wonder how he can get a shell like this to wear.
I may not be Dedede, but I’d still like to see how Escargon’s body works.
A snail without a shell is a slug.
That means, right now His Excellency Escargon is...
His Excellency, Slugscargon!
Don’t make light of my personal issues!
I’ll make sure you pay for this! Don’t laugh!
Oh, this one…!
This one looks like a perfect fit. You’re the only one who understands me, Kirby.
Now for what you’ve all been waiting for!
Ta-dah!
It really suits you!
Well, it is the same kind of shell.
Just be patient a while longer.
Nevertheless…
...stop standing around gawking, and get my shell fixed, pronto!
Got it?
Ugh. He’s so ungrateful.
Let’s just hurry and get it done.
To tell the truth, this is actually pretty nice.
Escargon! Escargon!
Eep! Not good...
Where are you?
What’s this?
This should be plenty strong enough...
Hey, there’s something inside.
Hey Waddle Dee, go set up the courtyard!
There. Looks like it’s holding together.
We should still be careful with it.
And here you have molluscs going their whole lives carrying one of these...
Poor things…
What is that delicious aroma?
There’s no way… It’s getting hot, I can’t breathe...
That olive oil, butter and garlic smell so good cooking together.
Your Majesty, that’s a splendid turban shell.
It smells delicious!
Grilled turban shell is a real delicacy. Since it’s so big I might share with you.
It’s getting pretty hot in here somehow!
Whoa, wait a second!
Help!
Kirby, inhale it!
Stop that!
Oh! Escargon!
Stop inhaling!
Were you pretending to be a snail when you were pleasant Sazae-san all along?!
(see notes in description)
Don’t be ridiculous!
That’s just an empty turban shell. Escargon was just inside.
So that means…
Escargon! How dare you eat that pleasant Sazae-san before I could!!
Did not! It was empty before I put it on!
It was, huh?
What’s going on inside that shell?!
Uh oh!
I give up!!
What are you doing?!
Escargon, don’t run away!
When it comes to my thirst for knowledge, I don’t know how to give up!
My age… is… catching up...
My my, if it isn’t His Excellency, Escargon.
That shell really suits you.
Even you! Laugh all you want!
I’m so sorry to have kept you waiting.
I’ll send your new shell, Your Excellency.
Escargon!
Oh no!
You in here?
Hey, Escargon.
It’s completely empty.
What took you?
What do you think of this?
Just a bit heavy...
This is Escargon’s new shell?
It’s our superalloy Heavy Metal Shell, mobile armored battle suit.
Enjoy yourselves.
Thanks!
Want to try your luck?
I have to know what you’re made of, no matter what.
Well if you really want to, give it a shot.
Here goes!!
Too hard...
Shell~
Shell shell...
Escargon, what have you...
That’s Maimaigon to you- shell.
Escargon’s…
...a demon beast!
Shell, shell!
You’re done for, Kirby.
That’s horrible, turning Escargon into a demon beast!
Fiend!
Begone!
Kirby! Inhale the hammer!
Got it!
Hammer Kirby!
Hammer Strike!
Oh that’s not working, what now?!
Shell… Mai Mai Beam!
Giant Swing!
Mai Mai Beam!
Exploding…
Hammer Throw!
He did it!
Lemme see… Lemme see, lemme see!!
Good work, Kirby!
Where’s Escargon?
I couldn’t see after all.
Ta-dah!
Thanks to that strong adhesive...
It should last a lifetime.
So after all that, Escargon’s secret...
I guess we’ll never know.
Escargon! Let’s go to the hot springs together!
No way! I see right through your schemes!
Let’s get to know each other better!
Don’t come near me! Don’t touch me! Stay back!
Just wait!
Nooo!!
Let’s just ignore them.
Kirby, you never got your chance to eat that grilled turban shell.
Emergency! Dedede wants to make another stupid anime, like “Dedede of the Stars”!
Because it’s impossible for the people in the village to do it, he hired animators from Holy Nightmare.
But the people making the anime are really weird somehow!
Kirby, we have to be careful next time.