By the way,
What's wrong?
They're really big!
Hey, tell me what do you eat to get like that?
There's nothing special really...
(Hey!)
(You idiot!)
Really? But how to get that big?
(You really shouldn't do this.)
(No one would do this kind of thing!)
Really? But how to get that big?
(I know that, obviously!)
(If I can achieve the goals,)
Good for you.
(it doesn't matter even if I forfeit my humanity!)
Look so good.
(Even if I become a demon!)
(You're too exaggerating, right?)
It's not like that!
(Just need to be self-control...)
("Self-control"?)
(No idea about that!)
(At least it's not in my dictionary...)
(Oh!)
Yume?
Your boobs are huge, Shihoru!
and they're cute, too.
Cute?
Yeah!
Is it okay if I have a feel of them?
(Don't hold back, Haruhiro!)
I'm just gonna touch a little bit!
(You've already lost to your instincts!)
(Otherwise, you would drag me back.)
(or raise your voice, right?)
Don't!
I knew it would be nice to touch them...
(I see...)
They're indeed amazing.
(I lost...)
(I lost, huh?)
(We lost...)
Wait!
(We...)
(You idiot! Actually...)
(we didn't lose...we won!)
Wait!
(What did you say?)
Let me touch a bit more!
(Our instincts...our desires won!)
Please don't touch me like that!
(Does it mean we lost?)
(NO!)
You're really like a little baby!
(We won!)
(Did I say anything wrong?)
You're really like a little baby!
(I see...)
That's amazing...
(So we actually won...)
(Without even noticing it...)
(and we won, huh?)
(But honestly, I am kinda curious.)
(Though I'm not really seeing anything.)
(I'm not gonna go and peek at least...)
(Of course, right?)
(Here are all our dreams.)
(Let's toast to that.)
(To this moment we are at)
(and to the meaning of being alive.)
(So, let the curtains for our dreams rise.)
It would be nice if mine are like yours, too, Yume.
But mine are just like this.
I think yours are very cute as well.
What? No way!
What do you think mines are cute?
They're not that overweight like mine,
but they seem soft.
But I don't think yours are overweight, Shihoru.
I mean, they seem soft and also seem tasty.
Tasty? I'm not the food, you know!
This is too much!
No, no, no!
What the heck are they two doing there?
This is too bad. My mind is all over the place.
Wanna take a bite? Maybe like here...
Maybe here?
Hey, don't hold back!
But it's gonna hurt...
Come here!
I...I can't.
Let me go, dumbass!
You stupid!
You're the stupid one!
Don't you wanna take a look?
Are you gonna give up such precious chance?
Are you really not gonna regret it later on, huh?
Well...
I might regret it.
I can't promise that I won't.
But what will happen if we go beyond?
What do you guys think?
What do you mean?
We're already excited now.
It'll be dangerous.
And we might gone too far to save.
So, let's head back to the room.
To our room.
The room for four of us here.
I don't think
I can handle that well.
Dammit.
Dammit!
Gosh dammit!
That shout was for all of us, from our hearts.
And it cried from our souls.
The unsettled feelings that can't be expressed
with the deepest of sorrows,
they were all drawn into the sky,
the starry night.
The red moon is hanging in the sky.
From the first time I saw it,
the amazing red moon stays still.
With an endless, deep dark blue sky,
the twinkling stars,
they're so close that were seemingly about to fall.
The desires of our souls,
must have shaken the faraway,
irreplaceable horizon of the beautiful world.
Guys, ride on me.
I'm fine with it.
It's raining?
That was thunder, right?
We gotta go hide somewhere.
Impossible.
This's impossible.
This can't be possible!
Moguzo's resolution is strong.
It's too strong.
Can we let go of everything to do this?
No, we can't.
There's no way we can do this.
Maybe our thoughts made the heaven waver.
Our desires also touched God's heart.
In this case, we should only go forward,
and continue to go this way.
Thank you, Moguzo.
We're alive.
Yes, we're still alive.
Now we can truly feel in this way.
That hurts!
Ranta!
No, this's not what you...
How!
You filthy fiend!
T-this is an open-air bath by itself, right?
(Staking Our Youths on the Bath Wall –
One More Centimeter)
Ranta, you idiot!
(Staking Our Youths on the Bath Wall –
One More Centimeter)
Dirty!
(Staking Our Youths on the Bath Wall –
One More Centimeter)
Filthy!
(Staking Our Youths on the Bath Wall –
One More Centimeter)
Pervert!
(Staking Our Youths on the Bath Wall –
One More Centimeter)
You'd better piss off and never come back!